const questionList = {
  easy: [
    {
      questionText: "When did WW2 begin?",
      correctAnswer: "1939",
      incorrectAnswers: ["1938", "1940", "1937"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "Who won the 2015-16 Premier League?",
      correctAnswer: "Leicester City",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Arsenal", "Tottenham Hotspur", "Manchester City"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "Which Harry Potter book is the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
      correctAnswer: "3rd",
      incorrectAnswers: ["1st", "2nd", "4th"],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "Which Italian town is the setting for Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet?",
      correctAnswer: "Verona",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Venice", "Florence", "Trieste"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "How many planets are in the Solar system?",
      correctAnswer: "8",
      incorrectAnswers: ["9", "10", "11"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "How many colors are in a rainbow?",
      correctAnswer: "7",
      incorrectAnswers: ["5", "9", "11"],
    },
  ],
  medium: [
    {
      questionText:
        "What 1949 science fiction book by author George Orwell describes a dystopian world in the future?",
      correctAnswer: "1984",
      incorrectAnswers: ["1982", "1986", "1988"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "Which country does not use the euro?",
      correctAnswer: "Poland",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Montenegro", "Slovakia", "Finland"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "Which company invented Angular?",
      correctAnswer: "Google",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Meta", "Microsoft", "Amazon"],
    },
    {
      questionText: 'Which astronomer is called out in "Bohemian Rhapsody"?',
      correctAnswer: "Galileo",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Copernicus", "Kepler", "Bayer"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "Which Croatian city is easternmost?",
      correctAnswer: "Dubrovnik",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Zagreb", "Split", "Slavonski Brod"],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "What song did Paul McCartney pen for John Lennon's son, Julian?",
      correctAnswer: "Hey Jude",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Octopus' Garden",
        "Yellow Submarine",
        "She Loves You",
      ],
    },
  ],
  hard: [
    {
      questionText: "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
      correctAnswer: "3",
      incorrectAnswers: ["1", "2", "4"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "What is the fear of women called?",
      correctAnswer: "Gynophobia",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Aranchophobia", "Trypanophobia", "Angrophobia"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "What is the calling code for Sweden?",
      correctAnswer: "+43",
      incorrectAnswers: ["+41", "+45", "+47"],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "In which city did the UEFA Champions League Final take place the earliest?",
      correctAnswer: "London",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Cardiff", "Kyiv", "Lisbon"],
    },
    {
      questionText: "What are the three summer Zodiac signs?",
      correctAnswer: "Cancer, Leo, Virgo",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Taurus, Cancer, Leo",
        "Leo, Virgo, Libra",
        "Libra, Cancer, Leo",
      ],
    },
  ],
};
